YU NGO TING OSCAR

STUDENT, POLYU

BSc (HONS) FINANCIAL TECHNOLOGY & ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE

YEAR3

AREA OF STUDY

- Data Science
- Programming
- Web development
- Cloud computing

LANGUAGE

- Cantonese
- Mandarin
- Engish

SKILLS

- Python
- JavaScript
- SQL Database
- Node JS
- React JS
- Firebase
- HTML
- CSS
- Figma
- Basic web scraping
- Δ\//
- Basic cloud knowledge
- Microsoft office

CONTACT

TEL: (852) 6681-5821

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/oscar-yu-

b8729a242/

EMAIL: oscar42302@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

I am looking forward to a career that I can work with others to develop E-commerce and provide customize customer plan through data analysis .

Adapting to new cultures and environments is something I am willing to do. Additionally, I am proactive in learning new skills and gaining expertise.

WORK EXPERIENCE

NETWORK QUALITY MANAGEMENT- SUMMER INTERN China Mobile Limited July 2022-Sep 2022

- · Data managing
- Assisting colleagues to complete the data visualization
- Making adjustment toward UI
- Conducting research/report

STUDENT ASSISTANT- PART TIME POLYU | JAN2022-JAN2023

- data handling
- · sending email
- · solving student enquiries

MARKETING MEDIA OFFICER - PART TIME

Maxway Service Limited | JAN2022-Present

- UI Design
- Video Editing & Scripting
- Web Handling through Customer Management System (CMS)

CURRENT PROJECT

- ECOMMERCE ONLINE SHOP
- PHOTO WEBSITE
- MOVIE TRAILER WEBSITE
- HONG KONG TRANSPORT INFORMATION WEBSITE
- HOTEL DATA WEB SCRAPING

EDUCATION

BSC (HONS) FINANCIAL TECHNOLOGY & ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE The Hong Kong Polytechnic University | 2020 - Present